tradeelectriclighting.ie 2016-12-05

# Trade Electric Group Privacy Policy

 P **RIVACY STATEMENT**

Trade Electric Limerick Limited (“we” or “us”) is committed to preserving the privacy of all visitors to [www.tradeelectric.ie](http://www.tradeelectric.ie/) .  Please read the following privacy statement to understand how we use and protect the information that you provide to us.

By using this site, you consent to the collection, use and transfer of your information under the terms of this privacy statement.

When you visit, register or order products or services on [www.tradeelectric.ie](http://www.tradeelectric.ie/)  you may be asked to provide certain information about yourself, such as your name, contact details and credit or debit card information.

We may also collect information about your usage of our website as well as information about you from (messages you post to the website and) emails or letters you send to us.

**Use of your information**

We use your information to supply you with goods or services ordered by you, to bill you and to contact you about an order.  We also analyse information provided by you and others to help us administer, support, and improve our business. 

We may use your information to contact you to tell you about important changes or developments to the website or our services, or to obtain your views on our services.

Where you have agreed, we may use your information to let you know about other products and services which might be of interest to you.  This contact may be by post, telephone, fax or email.  If you want to stop receiving information about other products and services, you can opt out at any time by contacting us (insert contact details e.g. email address).

**Disclosure to Other People**

We will never sell or rent your details to a third party.

We may pass aggregate information on the usage of our site to third parties, but this will not include information that can be used to identify you.

Unless required to do so by law, we will not otherwise share, sell or distribute any of the information you provide to us without your consent. 

**IP Addresses**

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the internet.  When you visit a particular web page in [www.tradeelectric.ie](http://www.tradeelectric.ie/) , our servers log your IP address.

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website.  Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small file sent to your browser from a web service and stored on your computer’s hard drive to identify you as the user of the website.  Many internet sites use cookies.  ** **

Our website uses cookies to keep track of our access to the site.  We may also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.  You can set your browser preferences to reject all cookies, but this will prevent you from using most customised services and you may have to repeatedly enter log in information in order to use some services.  Cookies make your experience easier by saving your preferences. 

**Security**

We employ security measures to protect your information from access by unauthorised persons and against unlawful processing, accidental loss, destruction and damage.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for a reasonable period or as long as the law requires.

**Changing Your Information**

You are entitled to see the information we hold about you.  The law entitles us to charge you a fee for doing so.  If you wish to see this information, please contact us 

You can also ask us to amend the information we hold about you to ensure that it is accurate and kept up to date.  Please contact us to do so [](mailto:Mizinka@hotmail.com)  

**Changes to Our Privacy Statement**

Any changes to our privacy statement in the future will be posted to the website and, where appropriate, through e-mail notification.
